Now, let's see how to print the link, Atlas notes.
The list consists of a number of notes, so I'm just remembering you with the basics of the linked lists,
the list or this list.
That injured list consists of a number of notes in which each node has in next pointer to the following
element to print the data and Lingard list.
We need to look through all the nodes and get the data section below that and of that list, so we are
interested in getting that data.
So the data inside the node, we need to print it, not the reference.
We need to print the note data.
So in sea, we need to loop through this element, these nodes, so we create a struct node dam.
These are that node.
This this is the link at least.
Pointing to null the last element, and we start by creating struck node temporary equal to hat, while
stamp does not equal to null.
So while that the reference to the next one is does not equal to null, then print f stamp, though.
And this dash, this dash is accessing that data inside the temp, so temp is referring as a had at
first and then it moves to the elements.
And temp tilt the.
Equal to none.
So while Tampa does not equal to none, loop through all the elements and get their data from that note.
So the first note is equal to IS had.
It contains number 18.
So the output will print that data, which represent 18.
It moves to the next one, which is metal, and bring the node of data and data of the node equal to
66.
It moves to the last one one one nine.
And print out that data and the note and it it's reference or the next is null, so it stops and break
the loop.
So in terms of time, complexity for scanning the list of size and it would be of NW, while the space
complexity is fine for creating a temporary fatti.
OK, so the time complexity of printing and ink and list is of and because we need to pass through all
the elements of this list and think about, we have a limited list of one million one million nodes.
We have all of one million.
So it is depending on the number of the nodes inside that linkage list.
Now let's print the link, at least in reverse order.
The list consists of nodes.
So this is their list and the same thing.
But here we have a different algorithm.
We start by printing reversely.
This is a method that we are going to create.
It took an parameter struct node to have.
We need to determine the hat and if have the equal call to null return.
So if the head is like reversing, it is equal to null, referring to null.
So that linked list is empty now.
But print reverse.
We are going to call the print reversely method in recursive way.
So we are passing ahead and next had next.
So we are passing the next element.
OK.
And print f the had data.
How this works.
We start by a print reverse leave from here had does not equal to none.
So it will call print reversely.
It starts from here and backward with recursion.
We start by executing that method that returns a result.
This is the basics of recursion.
We start by making it recursively and the last one, the last element that returns.
And now it will return so it will go back, reversely and print the elements back.
What?
Okay.
So it will print one one, nine, six, six and one eight.
This time complexity is of and for determining and printing the ink, at least in reverse the way.